neatgroup.com 2002-04-05

# Neat Group : Privacy Policy

**Neat Privacy Policy**

**ANY WRITTEN AGREEMENTS BETWEEN YOU AND NEAT GROUP, INC., INCLUDING ANY NON-DISCLOSURE AND CONFIDENTIALITY AGREEMENTS, ARE HEREBY INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE. IN THE EVENT OF A CONFLICT BETWEEN ANY PROVISIONS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE PROVISIONS IN ANY WRITTEN AGREEMENTS BETWEEN YOU AND NEAT GROUP, INC., THE WRITTEN AGREEMENT WILL CONTROL.**

#### WHAT KIND OF INFORMATION WILL BE COLLECTED?

Neat Group, Inc., ("Neat") does not collect any personally identifiable information but we do track individual login activity and gather data regarding site activity such as domain names, IP addresses, browser type, access times and pages accessed. 

Neat also uses cookies to identify your computer and maintain communications during your login session. A cookie is a unique identifier that is sent to your computer from a Web site's computers. While cookies do not personally identify the user, they do allow you to advance through the site without having to type your login name and password through each module. You can choose not to receive a cookie by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. However, please be aware that cookie refusal will reduce the quality of your online experience. 

#### HOW WILL THE INFORMATION BE USED?

Rest assured that any information collected by our site will be used only for internal purposes. We may use aggregate information about our users and visitors to improve our marketing efforts, statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content, services, and product offerings, and to improve our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses will improve our site and add value to your online experience. 

#### WILL INFORMATION BE SHARED?

Neat will not sell , rent, or share the information collected through our Web site with third parties unless there is an internal purpose for doing so. Occasionally, Neat may hire a third party to act on our behalf for marketing projects such as market research surveys and will provide information to these third parties specifically for this purpose. If we do, the project will be subject to strict confidentiality restrictions and will never reveal any personally identifiable information about you. 

#### CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Neat reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any material changes to this statement or in how Neat will use information will be prominently posted prior to Neat's implementation the change(s). 

#### LEGAL OBLIGATIONS

Neat may disclose any information if required to do so by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. Neat may also disclose any information against someone that Neat in good faith believes poses a threat to Neat's interests or whose activities could harm others.
